<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Fit Body</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>


    <string name="title_activity_login">LoginActivity</string>
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in or register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="welcome">"Welcome "</string>
    <string name="invalid_username">Not a valid username</string>
    <string name="invalid_password">Password must be >5 characters</string>
    <string name="login_failed">"Login failed"</string>
    <string name="logInText">Don’t have an account?  <font color="#E1EF63">Sign Up</font></string>
    <string name="signUpWith">or sign up with</string>
    <string name="log_in">Log In</string>
    <string name="forgot_password">Forgot Password?</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="username_or_email">Username or Email</string>
    <string name="welcomeText">Fit Body is a health and fitness app that helps users reach weight loss and other health goals. They provide food-tracking tools and curated meal and exercise plans that can be customized to fit your lifestyle. The central focus of Fit Body program is the logging</string>
    <string name="setupText">Consistency\n Is the Key To progress.\n Don\'t Give Up!</string>
    <string name="polices">By continuing, you agree to\nTerms of Use and Privacy Policy.</string>
    <string name="already_have_account">Already have an account? <font color="#E1EF63">Log in</font></string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="default_web_client_id">YOUR_WEB_CLIENT_ID</string>
    <string name="facebook_app_id">1320151189071003</string>
    <string name="fb_login_protocol_scheme">fb1234</string>
    <string name="facebook_client_token">5baa267d0422becd636b33c4cefa4071</string>
    <string name="fitbody"><b>Fit</b>Body</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy"> \n Effective Date: 2025 \n1. Introduction** Welcome to FitBody! Your privacy is important to us. This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, and protect your personal information when you use our application.\n2. Information We Collect** We may collect the following types of information: - **Personal Information:** Name, email address, and other account-related details when you register. - **Fitness Data:** Workout routines, progress tracking, and related fitness information. - **Device Information:** IP address, device type, operating system, and app usage data. - **Media Files:** Images or videos uploaded by users related to their fitness journey. \n3. How We Use Your Information** We use your data to: - Provide, maintain, and improve the MyFitness app. - Personalize your fitness experience. - Sync and store workout data with Firebase. - Enhance security and prevent unauthorized access. - Communicate updates, offers, or support-related information. \n4. Sharing of Information** We do not sell your personal data. However, we may share information with: - **Service Providers:** Third-party tools (e.g., Firebase) to help improve app functionality. - **Legal Authorities:** If required by law or to protect our rights and users\' safety. \n5. Data Security** We implement security measures to protect your data from unauthorized access, alteration, or loss. However, no online platform is completely secure, so we advise users to take necessary precautions. \n6. User Rights** You have the right to: - Access and update your personal information. - Request deletion of your account and data. - Opt-out of certain data collection and marketing communications. \n7. Third-Party Links** Our app may contain links to third-party websites or services. We are not responsible for their privacy practices, and we encourage you to review their policies. \n8. Changes to This Policy** We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify users of any significant changes through the app or other communication channels. **9. Contact Us** If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [fitbody.support@gmail.com]. By using MyFitness, you agree to this Privacy Policy.</string>
</resources>